Hello hello and welcome ministers, all of you are
welcome to today's Stock Delhi episode
number three in which we will know
about the performance of the market today, so
let's start, as you
can see Sensex-Nifty and Nifty Midcap
Fund because today they were seen trading in green
and we got to see a very good performance in it,
whereas Nifty Bank, like the previous trading
session, this time also Redmi also continued its
trend, as we all know that there has been a good trend
in our Indian stock market for the last many times, so
today
we again saw it continuing, it tensed up
by one plus six points i.e. zero
point way, Nifty remained stagnant
with 15 points, if we talk about the top banner, then
we saw Wipro in which we saw a
rise of 31 rupees
and Hitech which was
up by Rs. 25, if we talk about Infosys, then
profit booking was visible in it in the past in many ways, in which
we saw a rise today,
it was up by Rs. 30, if we
talk about India  In that too, we
saw wheat worth Rs. 100 today. Now let's talk about the
top losers. In this, we will see
Indian Oil Corporation, which was up by 1%. If we
talk about ONGC, then we saw a
decline of 1%. If we talk about Indian Bank, then
it was also down by 1% and Vitamin E,
we saw a decline of 1%. So,
these are today's top losers. Now let's talk about
which stocks held Nifty and
Sensex down today.
First in that is Reliance Industries, whose
current market price is running at Rs. 2429
and which set its 52-week high
near Rs. 2480 and from there it
closed at Rs. 2429. So, the reason behind the rise in Reliance was
that a subsidiary of Reliance made
its stagnation in the tender reference.
If we talk about the second set, then
it was Welspun India. The reason behind this stock
seeing a decline of almost 9% in the time was that it has
become the first company in India to be given clearance by the US
Food and Drug Administration.
Next is
ICICI Lombard in which we saw a
rise of four percent today. The
reason behind this, if you look at it, was that
IRDA had given approval to ICICI Lombard
for some work with Bharti AXA General Insurance.
Talking about the next stock, it includes
Eminem Financial Services.
Talking about Eminem Financial Services,
we saw a rise in this stock
because it had done a very good displacement in August.
If we talk about
Blackstock, then with the help of Noble,
we saw a rise of about two percent in it. So
these were some of today's news and we got to see a
very good mood of the market due to some stocks. So, to
get such videos, definitely subscribe to the Stock Bazaar channel
and share it with your friends.